sees.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy | See's Candies

| 

Effective Date: 05/19/2014

At See’s, we respect our customers' privacy.

This Privacy Policy explains when and how we collect, use and disclose Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) anytime you interact with See's, such as when you use our websites, mobile applications, and other related information and services provided by us (collectively the "Services", when you purchase See's products and services or call our sales or support associates and at other times. By accessing or using the Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

**Information We Automatically Collect**

We automatically collect information that does not reflect or reference an individually identifiable user ("Non-Personal Information") to help us understand how our users use the Services. As is true of most commercial websites and mobile applications, our Services use "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, how much time they spend there, etc. We also use cookies and other technologies to improve the quality and functionality of the Services and personalize your experience. Most Web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the Services will not function properly if you do so. We also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes, without limitation, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Web browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

We may allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you use the Services. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your use of the Services and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party Web beacon to collect this information. For example, we use pixels provided by a third party to track the number of end-user conversions we obtain from its paid search advertising, and a cookie provided by a third party will be placed on the computer of each end-user that clicks on an advertisement so that future advertisements can be targeted to that end-user based on the advertisements clicked on by that end-user. Our systems do not recognize browser "Do Not Track" signals, but several of our Service Providers (defined below) who utilize these cookies or Web beacons on our Services enable you to opt out of this advertising practice. To learn more about this advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can contact us at the contact information below and/or visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). We also provide you with additional tools to opt out of marketing from us or certain transfers of your information. You can learn about this in the "Managing Your Personal Information" section of this Privacy Policy. 

**Information You Choose To Submit**

We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, e-mail address or billing and shipping information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information ("Personal Information") that you choose to share with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to make a purchase, register on our Services, request a catalog, sign up to receive See's e-mails and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to provide such information, you may not be able to access certain areas of our Services. We may also receive Personal Information about you from third parties, such as from users conducting fundraisers through the Services and from those users' e-mail providers. 

**How We Use Personal And Non-Personal Information**

We use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as enhancing your experience using the Services; performing administration and technical support for the Services; notifying you about our new and existing products or services; gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole; and processing and fulfilling your orders and requests.

We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, marketing services, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, etc. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

We may combine information you give us through the Services or in our stores. We may also combine such information with publicly available information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes. We may also share or cross-reference, or cause to be shared or cross-referenced, such information, including Personal Information, with unrelated companies you may be interested in so that the companies can directly market their products or services to you.

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of See's or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 

We also may share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with companies affiliated with See's. In the event that See's is merged, or in the event of a sale or other transfer of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our opinion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that is different in an important way from this Privacy Policy.

**Managing Your Personal Information - Notice to California Residents/Your California Privacy Rights**

As set forth in this Privacy Policy, we offer our customers the ability to opt out of sharing your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the contact information below. You can contact us the same way if you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to update or delete your Personal Information.

Contact us at:

See's Candy Shops, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
20600 South Alameda Street  
Carson, CA 90810  
1-800-789-7337  

**Security**

We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us, including using SSL technology for encryption and transmittal of your order information (including your credit card information). However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Services, and you do so at your own risk.

**Children**

The safety of children online is very important to us. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a user under the age of 13, we will delete the information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page and the link to this page from our homepage periodically for changes. Those changes will go into effect on the Effective Date disclosed in the changed Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of the Services and will replace any prior Privacy Policies that are inconsistent. By continuing to use the Services, you consent to the changed Privacy Policy.
